Presented by DigiMovies website
:.:.: DigiMoviez.Com :.:.:
For information about the latest site address
: Follow DigiMovies on social networks
@DigiMoviez
"Translated by Ali Mohammadkhani, iredprincess and Soroush"
‫.:: SuRouSH AbG and iredsub
Good morning, ladies
hello
Hello!
thank you
Hmm
baby
I want your opinion
ok
what is it
Douglas fir parfait
Ah
honey, do you know what time it is? -
God bless you
Another test
Hmm
ok
So there is no trace of secretions, no stain, no liquid?
Aren't your shorts wet for no reason?
no -
What about the mucous plug? -
How do you know this?
very well
What liquids?
Didn't you ask me this question?
...No, I meant consumption. Liquid -
no, nothing -
God
Take care of your body water
ok
...so whenever you see any symptoms that
OK, I'll tell you first
Take it to the table
one more
table five -
OK, Chef -
Sauce?
Okay, it's ready
No worries, chef
very tasty -
Thank you, chef.
the chef
Don't you need anything?
No, it's not like that, I'm fine
let go Go back to the cartoon
So what happens now?
I recommend with
Start a course of chemotherapy
Why don't you cut?
Shame, I mean
Why not act?
to be honest -
yes -
It is very big
First we have to make it smaller
Let's slow it down
When we did this
Then we can act
What will happen next?
When you feel better after the operation
We need another course
undergo chemotherapy
Nothing should be left of the tuber
Given that your illness
has returned
There should be a treatment plan
Consider the upper hand
ok
... well
...just to be sure
...the first step
...a course of chemotherapy -
uhm -
His back strap is a surgery
After that, another course of chemotherapy
We hope it's the last? -
right -
Very good, great
What's the job?
What do you mean?
Well, in your opinion, let's calculate realistically
How long should he not go to work?
What do you think?
Well, according to the amount of physical activity of your job
To be honest, if you and your colleagues can
Find an alternative solution
I suggest you resign
Maybe it's time to buy a dog
I read somewhere that it was written
Pets, dogs
They help children
With the big problems of life
Beside expression
hmm
Because when with death
They face their bloodied animals
Their ability to
to wrestle with
Other problems increase
...So
You are saying to buy a dog
His life is premature
...to conclude, as a way to
Obviously, I don't mean to kill a dog
Maybe a very old dog
...if
...what would you say if I told you that
...I'm not sure that
I can do all that ding and feng again
Should I turn my back from the beginning?
...to assume
...suppose that
We believe that everything went according to plan
... and
No matter how long it took
...six or eight months
uhm
My illness will be completely cured and everything will be fine
Everything is Jehovah
Feel wonderful
yes -
It will be great like this. I agree, yes
But what if it is the other way around?
You are in a strange situation
You will find out
Instead of that six, seven
Eight or even nine months
You have used the last one
All you did was
You are bald and
You raised your heart and guts
uhm
very well yes
So you are saying in this scenario
...for you
Is quality more important than quantity?
I am saying that I have such a special interest in
A treatment plan that
Ironically,
I don't waste our time
I mean in that particular scenario
...I much prefer that we
A wonderful, wonderful moon
Let's experience the effect
Up to twelve months of nonsense and no activity
I don't mean that
I don't want to do the treatment
...I'm just saying that
I want to make the right decision
Simon Maxon: Hello!
"...I know it's been a long time
"Do you participate in the Golden Bokuz competition? »
[One of the most prestigious cooking competitions in the world]
"We need you in the British team!"
"I got my attention"
"When do you have time to talk?" »
knock knock
Breakfast is ready. do you have time -
yes -
Poranj or Nimro?
hmm
It doesn't matter
So the choice is mine
By the way, you are handsome
Thanks, Dad
Hello, my name is Tobais Durandeh
I am a member of Vitabix's IT team
I am responsible for monitoring the data
monster
Tell me, let's see
What did you eat for breakfast today?
Honey porridge with toasted bread
Then a bowl of Vitamix
very well
I think it is one of the positive points
For me, working in Vitabix is that
His party is private
Regardless, all of us
We gathered in this company from all over the world
...as well
We all have the status of each other's family
Dear Mr. Durand, we officially request you"
This divorce document before you have to
Implementation of the last order of the judge and termination of
Sign your marriage to Helen Durand
"Announcement of the request for finalization of the divorce decree"
"Sign here"
In Telegram:
@AliMK_Sub and @iredsub
very well
Divorce
Patient number 14
need the bed
What happened to my shorts?
If only I knew
...this... just that
That's all you had
Chocolate orange died on the scene
...Ah
By the way, my name is Almut
death?
death
Tobais
I'm sorry, but do we know each other?
seven
...yeah... no. Am
...shameful. i
I... got under you
seven
Patient number 17
shame
There is no problem
Hello and welcome to the red wagon restaurant
We are in the red wagon restaurant
We are proud of ourselves and our customers
Food with the taste of food
American restaurants of the 50s
Delivered alongside the Great Britain Road
All our burgers are based on
Our special recipe using
100% English meat and
Our expensive styles with
First-class ice creams are made
They don't have a skirt
what do you want
I am busy in Vitabix
Do you mean the same breakfast cereal?
uhm
... Well, our company
...shameful. Our company also owns
There are also Vitus, Applen and Red Burke. but yes
wow
You must be a very organized person
ah, ah
What are you?
I am a chef and a restaurant owner
oh
What kind of food?
do you cook
Modern European perspectives
Classic Alpine dishes
So, basically, Anglo-Bavarian
Well, at least that's my intention
We will open in a few weeks
how are things going
um...
oh
oh wow
No, it's going well
It will be great
You should come too
No, really, this is the least
I miss it
Bring your wife too
Am I beautiful? -
yes -
yes
There is something that
...I want a father
...something that mommy and I want
We want to talk to you about it
...yeah One problem
Honestly, it is an important issue
It's a serious issue -
yes -
Yes, it is serious
It's about adults -
yes -
It is serious, it is related to adults and it is important
yes
... Well, mommy didn't know, but
...Mom
How long has mom been sick?
It hurts
Severe and very bad heartache
...the doctors said that
Salam Alaikum! I see that the family
You came to eat ice cream and have fun
Junmi Jun!
My name is Noela
what is your name
My name is Ella and I am three years old
...sorry, we're in the middle
do you like that
Do I make this bottle disappear?
yes please -
Noel? Noel, I'm serious -
can't now -
now is not a good time -
Can you help me say the magic word?
Christmas!
Go... Get out of here. go
Shame, now is not the time
... well
what were we saying
uhm
I drank a lot of tea
Shall I make one for you?
All right, you two
It's time for your couple's bath and sleep
no
Do I need to follow you?
no -
did you nod -
I'm coming to get you now!
pick up teddy
what to do now
...you want me
...I don't think I can
sorry, mom -
No!
You fooled me
...we are going we have
I love him the most
yes -
me too -
I know -
Her hair is very beautiful, isn't it?
Really, very good this evening
You met him
...yeah, well
Yes, I'm glad we decided
Instead of killing a dog
Let's talk to him
yes
... well
...I was thinking
...maybe
...it's better that
...before starting my treatment
Let's have sex together
now
uhm
♪ The xx - I Dare You ♪
I wanted to say
Simon gave me a strange message
Simon Maxon, our previous boss, remember?
...well, um
He wanted to know that
I like you in the Golden Bokuz tournament
to participate or not
As soon as these events are over
We make sure that you
Enough time and opportunity for that
Go follow your interests
...but now
I think it's better not to rush
...focus on your treatment -
keep calm -
I told him no
I just thought it was interesting
That's it
Yes!
yala
It was great
A great throw
Thanks for the countdown
You joined us in the new year
what are you doing tonight
...you are going to go out and
Watch fireworks?
Stay home with your kids?
Are your friends going to show your house?
Call and
...tell us your plan -
thank you -
Hmmm!
Damn! screw it up
Oh!
They are officially getting more intense
hmm
Now the pain is every five to ten
They start once a minute
They continue for at least a minute
great thank you
see you very soon
There is nothing wrong with it
it's okay -
really -
yes, yes
Wait a moment. wait
Okay, okay, take your time
Waysa, waysa
very well
are you ready
Let's go
shame
screw it up excuse me
I can walk. I really say
damn sorry -
I'm serious -
Damn it!
It's ridiculous
I'm very sorry
damn
excuse me Very well, very well. how are you
yes
by himself well done
Your work is excellent
Yes, it is
very well
Well, mom and dad, the good news is that
The baby's heartbeat is good
Mom, so is your blood pressure and heart rate
Mom, unfortunately, the bad news is that
The opening of the vagina is still 2 cm open
Even less
So, I'm sorry but I have to
Go back home and wait
excuse me
Did you want to see me, chef?
Yes, come sit down please
...can be done
Can you close the door?
yeah sure -
Wow, sorry. No, no, sorry -
It was my fault
Chef, for that matter
Did you call me snails?
what No, no
no
Let me see, chef
...about...about matches
Do you need the room?
unfortunately
What do you know about the Golden Bokuz competitions?
...practically
Cooking Olympics
The highest honor
Sorry, chef, we're running out of celery
Keep it between us, chef
I'm serious, you don't say anything to any human being
...me
They asked me to participate in this year's competition
... to compete for the British team and
I want you to be my assistant
what -
But listen -
Oh God, the chef
There are two selection rounds
Let's pass to be accepted
...and you really have to consider something
Chef, I'm the base!
time time, chef -
You have to think about the time it takes
...Chef, practically the easiest decision
If we reach the European round
At least three or four days a week
We have to practice
If we reach the finals
It can be five days a week
Five days, full time -
Chef, I am -
We don't have any breaks -
I am hundred percent -
Let's get out of here
uhm
Yeah, probably better shaving cream
I will hit you on the back of the neck
It has become furry
really
It was great
Yes, that's right
We are jealous of you. do you understand
Jay Rayner recently published a controversial news
very well
very well -
go -
you leave
Very well, thank you. goodbye -
hello how are you
Did you make a reservation?
...yeah Tobai... Tobais Durand. I don't know
my god Mr. Vitabix
It was great
how is your hand look divine
oh
yes -
Well, listen -
We are very excited that you came to us tonight
We make sure the best
Have the time of your life
You reserved a table for two, right?
no
Shame, it's my fault
Myself and myself
No need to apologize
follow me -
ok -
I will inform the chef that you have come
A light meal to start
oh
Weisshurst Amos Bush
Or the same Bavarian white sausage
A modern change
Same method as lemon mustard gel. drink
thank you thank you
Hello -
How much would you give my little sausage from one to ten?
ten
I was sad to hear that your wife could not come
Is everything in order?
...Honestly, we are
...well, us
Technically, we are husband and wife
...legally
apart
We broke up
hmm
The back of your neck is so soft and smooth
My dad fixed it for me
Is there anything about hairdressing?
Architecture -
hmm -
How is the neck?
Yes, it's getting better
I don't think I've ever had the pleasure of sleeping with you
I have experienced a disease
um...
what is
I haven't practiced for a while
...and I just realized that
I don't have any condom with me
What a low expectation
... by the way
My employees want to know badly
Do you get VitaBix for free or not?
... well
I can confirm that
from time to time
to me
They give free VitaBix, yes
"Best Chef of 2010"
"Almut Brühl"
good morning -
...um -
Adrienne Duvall
We used to work together
oh
I didn't know that much
To be so competitive?
I should probably go
why
who said
I don't know
Um, you're right.
I don't know why I said that.
Of course, if you have work to...
I am unemployed
But if you...
If you have work to do...
I am unemployed
thanks
Hello, how are you?
- I'm fine, thank you
- Hello
It's time to test
Are you a cheese eater?
Do you like tapenade?
Your hand, sir
- Do you count these effortlessly?
- Yes
- Do you drink coffee?
- Yes, for sure
The reality was not like this
We had many bad days
We had little by little
We were thinking of having a baby
A job position in Sweden
It happened to the lady that
It was a very good position for him
After we talked about it,
We decided that I will stay here and
He will go to Sweden
Depending on the situation, either I would go to him
Or he comes here himself
But in the end, he came back and told me that
He does not want to continue this process
I'm sorry
Adrien insisted
Let's start thinking about starting a family
What did you want?
Um, I...
I guess you can say...
I don't get along well with children at all
let it go
I want to give you an egg
Eat your fingers with it
very well
You know the best way
What is to break the egg?
on a flat surface
Why do you have two bowls in your hand now?
practically
If the eggshell falls on it,
Removing the shell from inside an egg
Easier than 8 eggs
aha
Whatever I say about the flexibility of the egg,
Again, little
a few weeks ago
You said something to me
You said... you said absolutely with
You guys are not doing well
It's not like that, I'm serious
This is not the case at all. just...
The truth is, don't tell me, maybe with the kids...
Have a good time
and...
At least I think so
I hate...
I hate that even...
It... makes a difference, doesn't it?
At our age?
You are in a relationship with someone
whether you like it or not
You don't have much chance
Sorry, but exactly
What are you eating?
Well...
I prefer it myself
Now, let's be a bit confused with this discussion
Until we want five or ten years
Let's get along with war and fight
Please be advised that
First, I am 34 years old, not 55 years old
So what do you think about these poems?
Don't we see the growing age of feathers and wings?
secondly,
I know, my brain just says
Get out of me and
Pull yourself together
Where are you in such a hurry?
Honestly, it is possible
My throat is stuck in front of you
It shakes my body badly
Shame, I'm not human at all
I do not make such promises
Why lie? Even bringing it up has caused it
I regret what I did
hello
How was work?
um...
yes
- How was bedtime?
- It was not bad
We read the book "Julian the Mermaid".
For the thousandth time
Well...
The day we found out you were sick,
You said something to me
You said you prefer
A wonderful month
To experience the wonderful
12 months of nonsense and no activity
Yes, without any activity
That moment, because the answer
I was not clear and coherent,
I felt guilty
But what you said
It messed my mind badly
Now I have an answer
I want to share with you
ok
very well
um...
excuse me
"Although...
"Although previously,
"You...
um...
- Dad
- There is nothing wrong with it
don't rush
- I am stressed
- Sacrifice your head
um...
"Although...
"Even though before, you...
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry
- It's okay, do you want to...
excuse me
give
To hell with it
Yes, let's go to work
- Did I exaggerate?
- Yes
I'm out of water,
Now, whether it's one portion or a hundred portions
<font color="
pizza
anyone apart from pizza
Has a gentleman ordered?
give me
from...
- Vitabex?
- Hello
hello
- Well
Welcome to my sesame party
sorry for...
Resistance?
Last week, when I had
I was passing by the restaurant and saw you
mango...
It made me notice two things
let it be
First, I'm still mad at you
Because apart from that,
Maybe I misunderstood somehow.
But you also got over my embarrassment very well
Well, yes, it broke my heart badly
The second thing is that
I had a guilty conscience
Why was my focus in the wrong place?
I mean...
Thing, wrong angle
My focus was directly on the future.
Instead of exactly...
I want to see you in front of me
I knew he would do this
Do you like to cut mommy's hair?
Evil, yes. Open your little box
yes
You seem to be doing well
- Yes, nice and tidy
- As if...
- Don't talk!
- Well and...
He is himself
How much hair do you want to keep, mommy?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry
- Too many
- Yes, go on
- Horrible
Go down, Els
My flower girl
Hold her hair here for me, beautiful.
I'll go, sir.
Barikla, Baba's liver
- Excellent
- It is very beautiful
- Is it very beautiful?
very well
to to
oh
wow
how beautiful you have become
Isn't she very beautiful?
excuse me
- Yes?
- Are you happy?
yes
It has a capacity of approximately 200 to 600 guests.
Along with more than four hectares of private garden
to to
Also, it has a private parking
Marmara hall floor
With the architecture of Roman nobles
About 120 guests
For your evening reception
It reaches 140 people
You can also in our big hall
Play music and entertainment
Did you hear that, Els?
let's pay
Our greenhouse is in good condition
Reception of a maximum of 160 guests
He has dinner for the ceremony
or 200...
I touched his blanket
...for a self-service table
Spindle, accessories
Did you see the roof?
Unsaid example,
The use of drones in this collection
It is strictly prohibited
This one is around 20 minutes
It will take a long time, then it will kill your body
We prepare the use of the second dose
Be, thank you
very well Call us if you have anything
for sure
Dear chefs, how are you all?
Sorry for the delay
Technical problem cases
We apologize for the delay
The good news is that the viewers entered and
Ready and eager to start
Well, let me remind everyone
I will make an introduction
I will tell you about myself.
One about my role as
The head coach of the British team in the Golden Bocuse
We review the rules for a while and
What is today's plan?
Qualifying for the semi-finals of Europe and
etc. and these stories
We start a frenzy
excitement good
Is there a question? great
Alright, dear chefs. Forward!
- Salam Alaikum
Hello from us!
- What a wonder
- Yes
- Congratulations on getting a star
- Also
Yes, well, I guess...
I have passed my age
no
He is Jade Khadim, my assistant
- It doesn't matter
- Hi, Jade
go and leave
Really, amazing hair
- Thank you
- Yes
I will go to the bathroom
Fuck you!
Chef!
Chef, they are waiting for us
Nothing, I'm serious.
nothing special
Ella... now... I'm coming now
Chef, do you have anything?
what
Chefs can count too, Chef
no
No, I have stage three ovarian cancer
Do you want me to go?
Are we withdrawing from the competition?
No, I don't want to
Don't hurt your hand
Let's go to work
no problem right?
- Yes, that's right
- Excellent
very well
God is behind you
♪ Jess Glynne - Hold My Hand ♪
"The date of the European selection round has been determined"
"June 5th and 6th"
"The date is official"
"Congratulations again"
"You left a stone unturned"
hello
what are you thinking
- Hello
- Well...
I think I like this one
But in general I like both
"Almut and Tobais"
"June 5, 2023"
Can I choose tomorrow?
yes
Yes, for sure
what is
is something wrong
i am tired
very well
"Digi Movies"
Don't forget, um...
waterproof
- Who is it?
- We are!
Hello!
Very well, I will knock on the door to come up
arrive
very well
- Mommy!
- Hello!
- What a beautiful dress
- Yours truly
Honestly, they kind of mix
I'm sorry I didn't get you anything
Sacrifice your head, you have brought me another straw
- I brought straw for you
- Ben, how are you?
Shame on you guys
It hit the reeds. hello
- I can't believe it
- Hello, dear ones. please you
- Bye!
- Thank you
- How big is it?
- I know, I just got a bathroom
- With a double bed
- Ah, hello
carry on
- You came here for the first time
- How big have you really grown?
no Something came to my mind
- No words
- Yes, it's my first time
Oh my god, this little...
Hello!
Sorry, I don't want to disturb...
- Hi, I'm really sorry
- Hello
- I am glad to see you
- I'm Almut's sister, Leah
- I am Reginald
- Yes, he is my father
- I am very happy to see you
Reginald, it's an honor to meet you
- It smells amazing
- Thank you
- Also
- Hello, I am Almut's brother
- Lucas
- Welcome, welcome
Thank you, thank you
Well, it's not my house, but
I welcome everyone
Hi, I'm another brother, Ben
- Hello, hello
- I am glad to see you
Also
- Thank you
- You have authority
Bey said we should go to Salt Lake
He used to say that you will lose your mind when you see him
When we went, it happened to be winter
it is snowing
It was spectacular
We decided to go to Mishkan
- I don't know if you know where it is or not
- Yes, Dad
not...
Well, I lost track of time
We watched the sunset together
really...
believe me
The most unique day of our lives.
It was the same day
I returned there and told him:
"B, I don't know you,
But I guess I'm one
I want to be with you for the rest of my life."
Without any rings or anything
- I spoke my heart
- What did he say?
"You don't want to get emotional now"
"It is not necessary to have a hall full of people
It should be a sheet of paper
I understand that I want to be with you for the rest of my life."
- He said this
- Yes
- Amen
So you... When did you go to Salt Lake?
15 years ago
- Just around the corner
- Was it a business trip or a leisure trip?
what is What is the flow?
Me... the same year by chance
I had a competition that...
By chance?
- never mind
- Race?
what kind of race
The competition...
I used to work skating for a while
World Skating Championships
It was a battle
I can't believe you didn't tell them anything
- stop it
- Yes, yes
- look
- No
- Take a look
- You must see this
- Reginald
- My tongue is stuck
- It really doesn't matter
- That's it
Here it is
Oh!
- you?
- Yes, watch
Oh!
wow, my god
enough, enough you god I said no
I said no
- You should be proud of yourself
- Yes, unique
thank you, mom
yes
wine Does anyone not drink wine?
It's not just you, I didn't tell him
Thank God so far
I did not tell anyone
thank you
My dad made me go skiing
I think he really wanted it
Have an athlete child and
I think I was his last chance
I think...
He had the right to encourage me
Because the discoverer realized that
I love myself too
I was really talented in it
In the beginning, practically every weekend
They arrive in Swindon
After that, when he got sick,
It was unpleasant, I...
I wanted to help and
That's why I took a break for a while
After that...
After that story,
skating without my dad
I had no pleasure
Didn't you go after that?
I think he reminded me of my father in a bad way
how are you
- What happened?
- I think I'm getting sick
very well
Hey, hey, take it easy
I am cautiously optimistic that
We are dealing with an infection
But listen,
As soon as the liquid is removed,
We do some tests and
If we find anything,
We will be the first to inform you
- Very well
- Until then,
Some antibiotics for you
I write to start
It soothes your pain
- So?
- Uhm
- Thank you
- Please
Tobais, calling from the hospital today
They told me to go to the hospital and I went too
myself
It was not an infection
what is
I made a note
um
to recommend
or partial hysterectomy or
A complete hysterectomy should be performed
let's not skip the right
Your notes are extremely accurate
In desperation enough...
ok let me see...
The first option is that...
If we want to conceive naturally...
We have to freeze the embryos
uhm
- And then...
- Have surgery
In this way, they remove one ovary, not two
- After that...
- He has chemotherapy. damn
Canine chemotherapy
- Then...
- We have sex
Well, I don't know. IVF
(in vitro fertilization)
I say sex, but okay
Instead, the second option
Badly aggressive and
The risk of relapse is greatly reduced
They remove the ovaries and uterus
They take them all
very well
- I think
- Listen... I'm sorry
- No, you want...
- No, no. you
very well
I guess...
In my opinion, don't think for a while...
Crazy people, I think
My decision is that
One of the rotten ovaries
keep my cancer
because...
Simply because never
I didn't think I would be a mother.
There is no reason why I will never reach that level
Someday I can be by your side
I will take steps to have a baby
I am getting better
We must celebrate
Come on, come on!
- ...the throne or something like that
- What?
no
you are right
- Everything is great!
- Everything is in order
Vaisa, Vaisa, wait!
Sorry, sorry, sorry
tail
exhalation
a moment
Wow, I read you in this life
Feeling calm and relaxed
Almut?
Al? Almut?
run, run, run
Oh...
I'm going to get a drink
this...
Yes, it costs 20 euros with gasoline
thank you you did me a favor
thank you
hello
oh god
- Excuse me. thank you
- Hello
- Hello, how are you?
- Thank you, I'm fine
- Come on. Did you have gas?
- No, no
excuse me
Al?
Al? Al?
shame Excuse me a moment
Al?
- Hmm?
- Hello Is everything okay?
Hmm.. don't tell me
- What is it?
- Um...
Well, you know, I thought I had a toilet...
- Well
- Then...
- Now that I'm here...
- So?
I think I want to run
no No, no, no
No! ok
Sorry, but you can't
If you open the door, I... I can help you
We got biscuits, Al.
We have biscuits, okay?
- Okay
- Well, be quick. let me come to you
Oh no, I can't
what Well, just...
Unlock the door for me
i can't can't It seems... it doesn't work
wait
shame I apologize...
My lady is stuck in...
You have something... the key here...
- Yes
- I'm really ashamed...
- Thank you very much
- Hey, Jane, I just...
Well, Al, we got the key.
Here's the key, don't worry.
there is nothing
Shameful Mr
- No, no, it's not like that
- Thank you very much
well
Okay, just... just don't push it, Al
Whatever you do, just force...
Well, it seems... the key is broken
um...
- Do I say Al?
my darling?
I want you to stand back, okay?
- What?
- Go... back
- Stay away from the door
- Vaisa, Vaisa, let me see. why
Go back completely. As far as you can go. ok
- Why?
- I apologize to you very much
I think our baby is about to be born
- Yes...
- Maybe...
I... I'm going to get the jeans now.
Because he knows better...
- Okay, bring Jane
- Jane? Jane?
Jane, a pregnant woman is stuck in the toilet
- Please wait a moment
- Okay
The key broke in the lock...
- How many weeks is it?
- Fortieth
heh Congratulations
very well
You stay back, Al
- Shall I try too?
- Yes, yes
No, it can't be like this. no
very well
So Al, are you still holding back?
ok
- Hello
- I can't excuse me
What do you mean, you can't?
I can't eat shakes. excuse me
i can feel it
- No
- Uhm
- No, I know, but it's not possible
We have to... we can't...
No... not here
- We... no, can't... here...
- Listen and see what I say
- It is not a safe place
- The baby is coming. I'm sure
.yeah is coming
i feel it I feel beautiful.
excuse me I'm sorry
Excuse me, but... that... this...
is coming is coming yes
Yes, I think we have everything we need
We have it here now
except midwife
- Except for midwives
- Yes
Do I hear a clicking sound?
yes i think...
He probably wants to push
- Do you want to force?
- Yes
- Yes, he wants
Take care of your head. Be careful, be careful
Yes, I understand. He... can push
Al, Al, I'll have to check and see now
Do I see a part of the child's body or not?
no problem
I'm not in a position right now
I want to say no, am I?
very well
- Yes, I see his head
- Let me see, what?
- What? Tobias?
- Hiss. excuse me
- Vaisa, no, sorry, no
- Tobias? Tobias?
Excuse me, wait a moment.
Wait a minute, wait.
Well, listen to me.
You will get through it.
- Head?
- Sorry, sorry
Now I will put your voice on the speaker
Wait a moment.
can you.. please...
- Push harder, dear
- Okay
- Thank you Sorry, it's me
- Hello?
Can you repeat the end one more time?
Put your palm on each contraction
Look, you are doing great
On the woman's vagina
and press firmly and at the same time gently
- The child's head...
- Should I keep the baby's head inside?
- No
- No! O God!
- No, please don't do that
- No
Do not touch the child's head
- Keep inside the vagina
- That's right
You must press firmly and
At the same time, slowly enter that
Don't let the child
come out with great speed and
cause a tear
excuse me I'm sorry
Yes, I understand. i understood
- My God
- Did you understand?
Yes, yes, I understand now. excuse me
How is mother now?
How is mother?
oh tell him i feel
There is a big stone on my feet
He says that he feels like a stone under his feet
- A big stone!
- Excuse me
There is a big stone between his legs
yes
Is there anyone else there before you?
Yes, honestly, we... sorry
Sorry, I don't know their names
- I am Sanjaya
- Sanjaya
Hello, I'm Jane
- Hello
One of you please go
Make sure that...
The entrance door should not be locked and should be open
yes Here... here is the gas station
Yes, it's a gas station
You can come easily
Wow, I feel it, I feel it
His head is coming
is coming
Okay, that's it
yes come
Oh oh!
lean towards me well done
I see a face! I see a face!
I see a face! I mean the head
I see a head! great
His head came out
- Oh God!
- You are great
Yes, it's going great.
yes indeed great
You are doing great.
You are cracking up!
My God!
Very well, yes!
I grabbed his shoulder.
His shoulders came out.
it's over
yes it is over it's over
oh was born
- Yes, yes! You succeeded!
- Wow! my god was born
great It is wonderful
Baby daddy, is the baby crying?
is he breathing
yes
- Every shower, yes
- We succeeded!
- Wow!
you are wonderful
Now what I want you to do
This is to bring a clean towel
Very calm baby
Dry with it, okay, Dad?
- Yes. ok
- First, his nose and mouth
- OK?
- She is very beautiful
- Yeah, okay
- Very cute
- Can I see it?
- Yes, he is coming
Can you put the towel under it?
can i see it
I want to see him
- He is coming. is coming
- My God look at it
Don't hurt your hand, Sanjaya
- Hello
- That's your mom
This is your mom
I can hear your daughter's voice.
Did you say it was a girl? yes
yes a girl
yes yes yes
Mom and Dad, I congratulate you
Now I want a towel
Wrap your arms around your baby, okay?
- Yes, yes, okay
- Can you do this, Dad?
And without stretching the umbilical cord too much,
I want you to put the baby in his mother's arms, okay?
Al, Al, Al
And then I want that for sure
Keep mommy and baby warm, okay?
- Okay
- Hello
- I have you
- Yes
oh god Hello!
Wow, very beautiful
Thank you, Jane
Hey
Dad, I have good news for you
The ambulance will be there in a few minutes, okay?
ok
In the meantime, contractions too
It may start again...
Do you want this... Yes
Because the mother needs the placenta
also give birth
So I want you to
Take care and take it easy
- and keep it warm. ok
- Yes
OK, I'll do the same
yes
happy new year
happy new year...
Happy New Year
happy new year
Not only were we unable to shrink the tumor,
Rather, the cancer seems to have metastasized
has expanded
And that means, unfortunately
We don't have the right conditions now
We can do your operation
But there are still many reasons
To keep our spirits up
Other treatment methods too
It is still available
Failing the first time
Almost no connection and influence on
Secondary treatment is not likely to succeed
It is not like that. i am fine
i am fine I'm serious, I'm fine
yes
You have the right not to feel well
It is a heavy issue
You've had a hard time, mate
wow God
excuse me
my god are you sure
Now it is not the food of a noble person
thank you
Don't hurt your hand
what did you take
Twix
- Evil
- Yes
- What are you?
- Coconut bounty
I will not lag behind you anymore
I wanted to ask that...
I feel like it's 4 o'clock
take longer
I say you probably
Can't you go to kindergarten to pick up the child?
Of course, only if you have the time
- Definitely
- Thank you It will be great
I'll go, sir
Well, now we are 15 minutes late
your spit
twenty
your wedge Rest in peace, Dad. Vaisa
We went to Baga. This is not at all... we...
We are still very slow in preparation
This bag cooking technique too
- He is killing our father!
- Okay ok be calm
Let's rest for five minutes
No, I don't want to rest
I don't want to go to rest for five minutes.
I want to start again from the beginning
I have to look at our program.
I will check our schedule.
I have to think about what I should eat
I'm getting sick of this situation!
I'm sorry
You are also sorry.
Yes, you are right. Let's take a rest
Five minutes of rest
well what's next
- Octopus?
- Yes
Which grave were you?
you said you are going
- You cut from kindergarten
- I was a restaurant
- My God
- No
You weren't even in the restaurant, because I talked to Sky
He didn't know which grave you were
Now you went to look for the child... was everything ok?
No, not much
God
I had a bit left to go
I visit hospitals
I'm sorry excuse me really sorry
I am practicing for "Golden Bokuz".
hmm
- I didn't understand?
- Well... not the finale
It is only optional
Well... we won the national competition
how long is it
I see?
- How long have you been cooking?
It has become a more important priority for you
Until your illness gets better?
The national competition was in October and...
European elections will be held soon
Does the hospital know?
They know that...
They know... you are God
please please say that...
that they know you...
What is the difference between knowing or not knowing?
Wow, can you be big Almut?
you have cancer
Al, you have cancer
No, grow up, you moron
The difference is...
too much
why Why are you taking such a risk?
- Isn't it clear?
- No, by the way, it is not
- It is not clear to me
- Well then
I won't get such a chance, okay?
What does this mean then?
exactly...
It means that I don't like when I die
I have no achievements in my life
oh ok
So you mean we... we are not enough for you?
yes Is this the case?
Proud chef and
Mental figure skater...
No, you are being cowardly
No, no, no, I have no such intention
I'm really... trying to figure it out
what causes
A wise person wants...
Of course I count you, bitch!
OK, so I don't get it
excuse me
But I really...
By God, I don't understand
Maybe... oh my God!
That is, it has not occurred to you yet
Maybe I don't like it
Just be someone's dead mother?
I mean, nothing at this moment
It doesn't scare more than this...
Thinking that he
It will have nothing
Remember me with it
And as if... there is a part of me
Doorway wants to know that
I did not give up easily
And wouldn't it be really nice if
Maybe that one day
He decided to remember this time.
He really decided to look back
To this damn situation we are stuck in and
Say to yourself:
"Oh my god, is that my mom?"
I don't want...
I don't want Ella's memory from me
Only let me decline and weaken
Or maybe I imagine that I will be forgotten
It is unbearable for me
I really don't know which one is worse
That you want us with your achievements
let's remember
Something and...
That wants you with achievements
Let's remember that
We have no information about them...
OK, I get it, I messed up
Ridham please stop
please
Please don't stretch anymore
who is it now
The same race?
European selection, or I don't know what?
June
June?
June, thing...
June 5th and 6th
correct
I'm really sorry, Tobias
I really say
"Almut Bruhl and Tobias Durand's wedding invitation"
In Telegram:
@AliMK_Sub and @iredsub
"Skate Hall"
Because of aerodynamics, right?
Chef, I think I'm getting high
oh shit Excuse me, you... have a bucket...
Did you see a bucket?
Or a glass of something...
Well, go ahead
very well
- Did you get better?
- Yes, chef
Chef, sometimes only
Your heart and intestines want to spill out
- Solve it?
- Yes
- Let's go to work
♪ Avicii - Levels ♪
Please encourage the British representatives.
Almut Brul and Jade Khadim
Come on, England! I can't hear your voice!
An admirable start
By presenting a plate
Please encourage the representatives of Norway.
Viggo Hansen and Søren Hansen
Come on, English!
"Leave me, mom!" »
Ready, go!
let's go
Britain
Start!
That's your mom
- Team Britain! British team!
- Great Britain!
Well done, Great Britain
Very well, give it to them
yes, yes Yes, we give now
was prepared
- Thank you
- Greetings to you
very good
Well done mom!
Well done Almut!
oh
Go, go, go...
(Golden Bucs of Europe)
British team
Thirty seconds to go
My soul, Almut!
- Continue!
- Until the last minute, guys!
Only a few seconds left. Come on!
Ten, nine, eight...
Seven, six, five, four
Three, two, one
Evil! Excellent!
- Is it good?
- Yes
- Yes. yes
One, two, three
- Britain!
- Well done, you are hot
He succeeded. did it
i did it
You were wonderful
i love you
the chef
See you soon, chef
wow hello
then
let's go
are you ready let's go
we turn
good
- Okay Look at Mommy
- Well
gone
Goodbye, Mommy!
Bye bye!
Kiss!
"Translated by Ali Mohammadkhani, iredprincess and Soroush"
‫.:: SuRouSH AbG and iredsub
For information about the latest site address
: Follow DigiMovies on social networks
@DigiMoviez
very well
ok
Let's put them on the table, shall we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Because now is the time to harvest eggs
Hi Belinda. Hi Berry
how is this
- Is it good?
- Yes. yes
- Put it in the basket
- Yes
Put it in the basket, please
Will you check this for me, please, egg manager
How many would you like, honey?
five
Take as many as you like.
Five is good.
- Yes
- Wow, look at this
- Yes. yes
One, two, jump! Wow jump!
Well, you remember
What was the best way to break an egg?
You always put it on
A flat surface, right?
- Yes
- Then you throw it in
went there
do you want to try
you can you can
Open it a little
Well done, you did it
Vaisa
It was great
It does not have a shell
Don't you have a shell?
- Okay, well now...
- Yes?
bye bye
goodbye
Presented by DigiMovies website
::.:.: DigiMoviez.Com ::.:.:
♪ Romy and Sampha – I'm on your team ♪